They're converging And we
think that growth is
going to in the
next few years So
here we ask the
non farm productivity increase
above 3 in
any quarter This is
on a year over
year basis in any
quarter in 26 And
you can see there's
a 42 probability
Well we think the
actually is much higher
than that And it's
actually for a statistical
reason If you look
at productivity today you
can see we're at
2 5
And you can also
see again if you
look across this chart
this is in the
higher half of the
of this So
pretty strong And
as we have said
in the know many
times we've in a
rolling recession And this
is what has happened
That's so interesting Housing
has been down and
out Manufacturing's been down
and out Small business
down and out Consumers
have been in funk
as measured by sentiment
And productivity is at
2 5 So we
believe that these technologies
are already having an
on productivity